Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: IUE-AFL-CIO-CLC Policy Statement on Equal Employment Opportunity, 1966; Publication (Box 153, Folder 5)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Handbook on collective bargaining techniques, Publication (Box 153, Folder 6)
    Author: James Trenz
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Agreement between American Bosch, Divisions Ambac Industries Incorporated, Springfield, Mass. And Local No. 206, International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers A.F.L.-C.I.O., effective May 12, 1980, Publication (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: District 3 IUE, AFL-CIO, 4th Quarterly Financial Statement, 1959; Publication (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: District 3's Challenge for tomorrow a hard punching education program, 1956; Publication (Box 153, Folder 7)
    Author: Ed Grabowski
  - Item 4: IUE-AFL-CIO, Eighth Constitutional convention, 1958; Publication (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Statement of International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO-CLC and Coalition of Labor Union Women before the Equal Opportunity Commission on 'Job segregation and wage discrimination under Title VII and the Equal Pay Act', 1980; Publication (Box 153, Folder 7)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: 8th Convention, District 4, IUE-AFL-CIO: Officers' report, the Concord, Lake Kiamesha, New York, Sept. 2, 3,4,5, 1958, Publication (Box 153, Folder 8)
    Author: International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers. District 4.
  - Item 2: District 4 IUE-AFL-CIO, Union Leadership Academy, 1957; Publication (Box 153, Folder 8)
    Notes: Workshop paperwork
  - Item 3: Education Committee Newsletter, 1956; Publication (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Handbook on collective bargaining techniques, Publication (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Newsletter, 1954; Publication (Box 153, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.2,8 (1954:Feb.)
  - Item 6: Newsletter, 1953; Publication (Box 153, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.6 (1953:Nov)
  - Item 7: The story of the Westinghouse Strike, Publication (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Toward an understanding of time study problems and a trade union approach, 1954; Publication (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: What happens to your contract?, 1940; Publication (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Winning Grievances, Publication (Box 153, Folder 8)
    Notes: Booklet about grievance procedures done like a comic strip
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Engineering News, 1960; Publication (Box 153, Folder 9)
    Author: IUE, District 4
    Notes: vol.1, no. 1-3
  - Item 2: Engineering News, 1961; Publication (Box 153, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.2, no.1
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: District 4 News, 1956; Publication (Box 153, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.1, no.2-4
  - Item 2: District 4 News, 1957; Publication (Box 153, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol. 2, no.1,3-4,6-7
  - Item 3: District 4 News, 1958; Publication (Box 153, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.3, no.1
  - Item 4: District 4, IUE-CIO, 1954; Publication (Box 153, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol. 3, no.1-3 (1954)
  - Item 5: District 4, IUE-CIO News, 1953; Publication (Box 153, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol.1, no.4,10-11, vol. 2, no.5-7, 9 (1953)
  - Item 6: Salaried Digest, 1956; Publication (Box 153, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol. 1, no.2 (1956)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Arbitration and your local union, Publication (Box 154, Folder 1)
    Author: IUE, District 8
  - Item 2: District 8, IUE-CIO: A program for skilled trades, 1953; Publication (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Labor History, an outline of the struggles and efforts of the American worker, Publication (Box 154, Folder 1)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report of General Electric Conference Board; Report of Progress in pensions, 1955; Publication (Box 154, Folder 2)
    Notes: Conference materials. IUE-CIO 1st Economic Policy Conference
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Fundamentals of time study, 1953; Publication (Box 154, Folder 3)
    Notes: Leadership training materials
  - Item 2: Instructor's manual, 1951; Publication (Box 154, Folder 3)
    Author: International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers. District 7. Educational Dept.
  - Item 3: Org. meetings social events, fund raising, bulletins, political action, 1954; Publication (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Parliamentary Law for Union Officers - Grievancemen & others who handle meetings, 1952; Publication (Box 154, Folder 3)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Arbitration: arbitration procedures and techniques, 1957; Publication (Box 154, Folder 4)
    Author: International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers. District 7
  - Item 2: Did you know? Service is a big word, 1951; Publication (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Grievances: requirements for good leadership, investigating grievances to win various types of grievances keeping proper union records, quiz...writing grievances properly, 1956; Publication (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: How foreign is 'foreign' competition?, 1971; Publication (Box 154, Folder 4)
    Notes: Reprinted from the UE News
  - Item 5: Parliamentary Law: recommended for use by Union Officers, Union Chairmen, Stewards, and others who participate in Union meetings, 1956; Publication (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Security?, 1951; Publication (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: The Grievance procedure ..., 1962; Publication (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: The Grievance procedure ..., 1956; Publication (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Time study, 1956; Publication (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Why is it necessary and important?, 1953; Publication (Box 154, Folder 4)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Legislative effectiveness, Publication (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Officer and Steward training, Publication (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: The Campus comes to you, Publication (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Why labor is in politics, Publication (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Announcing Miami University (District Seven, IUE, AFL-CIO, Leadership Training Institute), 1965; Publication (Box 154, Folder 5)
    Notes: Advertisement flyer
  - Item 6: Collective bargaining procedures and issues for labor unions, Publication (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Constructive political action, Publication (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Cope information., 1964; Publication (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Don't trust to luck, 1965; Publication (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Using education in your union, some suggestions for local unions, 1952; Publication (Box 154, Folder 5)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Background on collecting, 1960; Publication (Box 154, Folder 6)
    Author: International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers. Education Dept.
    Notes: i. e. collective bargaining issues
  - Item 2: IUE leadership manual for shop stewards, 1958; Publication (Box 154, Folder 6)
    Author: International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers.
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: IUE handbook for local union officers, 1962., Publication (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: IUE leadership training manual, 1960., Publication (Box 154, Folder 7)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: An insider looks at labor unions, 1959; Publication (Box 155, Folder 1)
    Author: Ben D. Segal
  - Item 2: Inside IUE, 1959; Publication (Box 155, Folder 1)
    Author: International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO.
  - Item 3: Script for a mock meeting, Publication (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Some efforts at democratic union participation: a paper, 1958; Publication (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: The people vs. the profiteers: from the testimony of Ralph J. Cordiner, chairman of the Board of Directors General Electric Co., before the U.S. Senate Subcommittee on Anti-Trust and Monopoly, Publication (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: This is our union, Publication (Box 155, Folder 1)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: IUE handbook for local union officers, Publication (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Teaching guide on local union administration, 1959; Publication (Box 155, Folder 2)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: GE propaganda: a study in deception, 1960; Publication (Box 155, Folder 3)
    Author: International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO. Education Dept.
  - Item 2: How foreign trade affects you, Publication (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: How secure is your job!: operation information, Publication (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: International trade union solidarity strengthens the free world, Publication (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: IUE Latin American trade union project, Publication (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: IUE leadership manual for shop stewards, 1958; Publication (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: IUE looks at a world in crisis, 1962; Publication (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: IUE speed learning leadership manual for shop stewards, Publication (Box 155, Folder 3)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Dedication of James B. Carey Library, IUE Presentation Speech, Institute of Management and Labor Relations, Rutgers Univ., Oct. 20, 1962, Publication (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Reading selections for IUE Leadership Training, 1961; Publication (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Teaching guide on local union administration, 1959; Publication (Box 155, Folder 4)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Grievance handling techniques: suggestions to build and strengthen your local union, Publication (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: IUE members' guide, College Education financing, 1966; Publication (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Speech transcript Education should be an active part of your local union, 1965; Publication (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Your union welcomes YOU, 1968; Publication (Box 155, Folder 5)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Code of ethical practices, 1957; Publication (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: IUE-AFL-CIO Code of ethical practices, 1957; Publication (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Memo - Organization report by Secretary-Treasurer Al Hartnett, 1955; Publication (Box 156, Folder 1)
    Author: Al Hartnett
  - Item 4: Report to Executive Board by James B. Carey, Hotel Statler, Washington, D.C., Jan. 23-24, 1953, Publication (Box 156, Folder 1)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Facts of the month IUE-CIO, 1953; Publication (Box 156, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.1, no.1,4 (1953)
  - Item 2: Facts of the month IUE-CIO, 1954; Publication (Box 156, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.2, no.1-12 (1954)
  - Item 3: Facts of the month IUE-CIO, 1955; Publication (Box 156, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.3, no. 1-6, 8,10- 12 (1955)
  - Item 4: Facts of the month IUE-CIO, 1956; Publication (Box 156, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.4, no.3-8,10-12 (1956)
  - Item 5: Facts of the month IUE-CIO, 1957; Publication (Box 156, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.5, no.3-5,77 (1957)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: On strike at G.E., labor's fight on the IUE picket line, Publication (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Exposed! UE's shameful record on Communism!, 1955; Publication (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Federal Grand Jury says UE Leaders' non-Communist oaths, 1965; Publication (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Help wanted, Publication (Box 156, Folder 3)
    Author: General Electric Company
    Notes: flyer telling the stories of some laid-off employees of the General Electric Company
  - Item 5: IUE puts the spotlight on GE, 1966; Publication (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: IUE-CIO economic program, 1954; Publication (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: No deals with UE!, 1965; Publication (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Why there is a strike at General Electric: a statement, 1960; Publication (Box 156, Folder 3)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Does GE want industrial peace?, 1952; Publication (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: IUE-CIO News, 1951; Publication (Box 156, Folder 4)
    Notes: 1951 Aug. 28
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: An open letter to UE members in the GE chain, 1960; Publication (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: An open letter to UE members in the GE chain, 1965; Publication (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Memorandum - to General Public, from IUE, Re Facts on General Electric Strike, 1960; Publication (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: On strike at G.E., 1960; Publication (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: On strike at G.E., 1965; Publication (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Report...on the 1960 GE Strike, Publication (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: We have no choice, 1960; Publication (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: We have no choice, 1965; Publication (Box 156, Folder 5)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Inside IUE-CIO, 1955; Publication (Box 156, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.5, no.15-16 (1955)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Reports on Domestic Program, Political Action -- at the 6th Annual Convention of the IUE, 1954; Publication (Box 156, Folder 7)
    Notes: Speech transcripts
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: IUE-CIO News, 1951; Publication (Box 156, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol. 1, no. 1--3,5-20 (1951). 2 copies
  - Item 2: Schenectady IUE-CIO, 1950; Publication (Box 156, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol. 1, no. 13 (1950)
  - Item 3: The IUE-CIO News - IUE-CIO Campaigner, 1950; Publication (Box 156, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol. 1, no.9 (1950)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: We speak for experience., 1950-1959 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: 1936 to 1954, Local 301 pioneered equal pay for equal work, 1950-1959 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Expose of collusion..., 1950-1959 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: IUE-CIO, The Union that is stopping the run-away shops!, 1950-1959 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Local 301 IUE, Flood victims need your help, Publication (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Local 301 IUE, Want to know more about prepaid group health services?, Publication (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: No total victory, General Electric, Local 301, 1960-1969 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: The truth about seniority, 1950-1959 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: The UE, bankrupt financially as well as politically!, 1960-1969 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: To All Schenectady GE Production Workers, 1950-1959 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: Election report to GE Workers, from Local 301, IUE-CIO, 1960-1969 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: He commands respect of bargaining foes, 1960; Publication (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: John Maguire's profiles, Leo Jandreau, 1960; Publication (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Local 301, IUE-CIO Shop Stewards' - Bulletin and Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 156, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.2-7, 11-12
  - Item 15: Meet the Candidates, Unity Slate, Publication (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Item 16: Our contract: it must be improved and the only way to do it is by uniting all GE workers in one union!, Publication (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Item 17: Stewards' classes discussion outline, 1960-1969 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Item 18: UE-301, with 20,000 members, 1950-1959 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Item 19: UE's Record in GE since 1948, 1960-1969 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Item 20: Unity Slate vote Shambo - Kelly - Jandreau, vote against disruption, 1950-1959 (Box 156, Folder 9)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: 301 IUE-CIO News - Turbine 2nd shift, UE unity exposed, 1954; Publication (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: IUE-CIO News - There's no place like home!, Publication (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: IUE-CIO News, Labor Day Rally (Sept. 14), Publication (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Local 301 News, 1954-1955 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.1, no.12-21,28-29,31,33-34,36-37,40-45 (1954- 1955)
  - Item 5: Local 301 News, 1958-1959 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.4, no.31-32,34-45,47 (1958-1959)
  - Item 6: Local 301 News, 1959-1960 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.5, no.48-51,53-55-58 (1959-1960)
  - Item 7: Local 301 News, Publication (Box 157, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.6, no.1,8-9,12,16,18
  - Item 8: Local 301 News, Publication (Box 157, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.7, no.2-3,7-8,11,13,15,17,19,24,-25,28,31,33-34,36
  - Item 9: Local 301 News, 1963; Publication (Box 157, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.10, no.29,32 (1963)
  - Item 10: Organization diagnosis and improvement strategies, 1973; Publication (Box 157, Folder 1)
    Author: Harvey A. Hornstein
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: article - Industrial Social Work - Problems and Prospects, 1978; Publication (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Local 301 News, 1960; Publication (Box 157, Folder 2)
    Notes: Special issue (Sept. 1960)
  - Item 3: Local 301 News, 1960; Publication (Box 157, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.7, no.37-45 (1960)
  - Item 4: Local 301 News, 1961; Publication (Box 157, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.8, no.1-2 (1961)
  - Item 5: Local 301 News, 1962; Publication (Box 157, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.9, no.24-26,31-41,43-50 (1962)
  - Item 6: Local 301 News, 1965; Publication (Box 157, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol. 12. no.5-18,20-25,27-28 (1965)
  - Item 7: Local 301 News, IUE-AFL-CIO, 1967; Publication (Box 157, Folder 2)
    Notes: (1967:Nov. 30)
  - Item 8: Newsletter from the Radio Officers Union, UTW, AFL-CIO, 1979; Publication (Box 157, Folder 2)
    Notes: (June 1979)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Local 301 News, 1963; Publication (Box 157, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.10, no. 2-3,5-9, 11, 18,24, 26-27,33-39, 41,43-44
  - Item 2: Local 301 News, 1964; Publication (Box 157, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.11, no. 1-2, 4- 13
  - Item 3: Local 301 News, 1964; Publication (Box 157, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.11, no. 13-43,45- 46
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Local 301 News, 1967; Publication (Box 157, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.1, no.1-4,6- 10
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Local 301 News, 1965; Publication (Box 157, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.12:no.1-7, 9-12, 50- 52
  - Item 2: Local 301 News, 1966; Publication (Box 157, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.13:no.1-2,4-13, 15-17, 23, 26-45,47-49
  - Item 3: Local 301 News, 1967; Publication (Box 157, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.14:no.1-2,4-5,11,16- 21
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Local 301 News, 1974; Publication (Box 158, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.8:no.3-4,6,8-13 (1974)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Local 301 News, 1973; Publication (Box 158, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.7:no.1,3-9,12,14,17,19-23 (1973)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Local 301 News, 1972; Publication (Box 158, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.6:no.1-24 (1972)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Local 301 News, 1971; Publication (Box 158, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.5:no.1-7,9-20,22-24 (1971)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Local 301 News, 1970; Publication (Box 158, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.4:no.1-21 (1970)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Local 301 News, 1969; Publication (Box 158, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.3:no.1-13,15-16,18,20 (1969)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Local 301 News, 1968; Publication (Box 158, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.2:no.1-2,4-7,9-12,14-24 (1968)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 158, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Local 301 News, 1967; Publication (Box 158, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol.1:no.12,14,15 (1967)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Local 313 News, 1958; Publication (Box 159, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1958 (Apr.)
  - Item 2: Local 313 News, 1959; Publication (Box 159, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1959 (Feb.-Sept., Nov.)
  - Item 3: Local 313 News, 1962; Publication (Box 159, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1962 (July-Aug.)
  - Item 4: Local 313 News, 1965; Publication (Box 159, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1965 (May, Aug.- Sept.)
  - Item 5: Local 313 News, 1966; Publication (Box 159, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1966 (Oct.)
  - Item 6: Local 313 News, 1967; Publication (Box 159, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1967 (Jan., Mar., June, Oct.)
  - Item 7: Whisper-Not, 1968; Publication (Box 159, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1968 (Sept.-Dec.)
  - Item 8: Whisper-Not, 1969; Publication (Box 159, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1969 (Mar.-May, July, Sept.- Dec.)
  - Item 9: Whisper-Not, 1970; Publication (Box 159, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1970 (Feb-June, Sept.)
  - Item 10: Whisper-Not, 1971; Publication (Box 159, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1971 (May-Dec.)
  - Item 11: Whisper-Not, 1972; Publication (Box 159, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1972 (Jan., June-July, Sept.)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Local 313 News, 1958; Publication (Box 159, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1958 (Sept.)
  - Item 2: Local 313 News, 1959; Publication (Box 159, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1959 (Oct.)
  - Item 3: Local 313 News, 1960; Publication (Box 159, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1960 (Nov.-Dec.)
  - Item 4: Local 313 News, 1961; Publication (Box 159, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1961 (Jan.-Nov.)
  - Item 5: Local 313 News, 1962; Publication (Box 159, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1962 (Feb.-June, Oct.)